flowers What minute do I put okay I'm going to
flores Qué minuto pongo vale voy a
put it here okay I don't know if I'm going to
ponerlo por aquí vale No sé si lo voy a
see it all But anyway let's see it okay
ver entero Pero bueno vamos a verlo vale
tell the whole circle of gindi The
cuenta a todo el círculo de gindi El
problem that there was in Tania's life or
problema que había en la vida de Tania o
what problem Tania went through in the past
por qué problema pasó Tania en el pasado
Ah what is Tania talking about Let's see is that they
Ah que est hablando Tania A ver es que
blame Consuelo for having
culpan a la consuelo de de haber
leaked, for having told us about
filtrado de habernos contado lo del
Tania's problem I mean Consuelo didn't
problema de Tania o sea Consuelo no
know the problem in Tania's life let's
sabía el problema en la vida de Tania a
see she knew eh she knew another version No the
ver sabía eh sabía otra versión No la
truth she knew a much more
verdad sabía una versión muchísimo más
like version in fact Tania compared the
like de hecho Tania comparaba el
problem in her house she compared it
problema que hay en su casa lo comparaba
to Antonio David's problem touch your
con el problema de Antonio David tócate
balls touch your balls eh of
los [__] tócate los cojon aos eh
course then Consuelo didn't know the
claro entonces Consuelo no sabía la la
reality that has been known Consuelo didn't
realidad la que se ha sabido Consuelo no
know she couldn't tell us she didn't
lo sabía no nos lo pudo contar no lo
know we imagined me by
sabía nosotros nos imaginamos yo por las
Loli's very clear insinuations we took
insinuaciones de Loli muy claras dábamos
for granted that something existed not some
por hecho que existía algo no unas
accusations of abuse that I did say
acusaciones de maltrato que yo sí decía
well in this case no
bueno en el caso este no aparece ninguna
sentence of anything appears they went directly
sentencia de nada se fueron directamente
to the Source of the  chain.org the Source of the
a la Fuente del chain.org la Fuente del
chor Tania pringao they went
chor Tania pringao se fueron
directly to the Source of the chor the
directamente a la Fuente del chor la
Source of the chor Tania pringao they went
Fuente del chor Tania pringao se fueron
to the Source of the chor as if it were a
a la Fuente del chor como si fuera una
source if that source was Tania and they say
fuente si esa fuente era Tania y dicen
that in this name the case and it was
que en estaba nombre el caso y estaba
everything was [ __ ] to locate
todo estaba una [__] para localizar
that case was on a blog of Tania it
ese caso estaba en un blog de Tania
has to be a lawyer the one who enters what the hell is
tiene que ser un abogado el que entre en
this clown talking about guy
la qué coo está hablando este payaso tío
this guy is an idiot eh website that
este tío es idiota eh página web que
they have a lawyer on the
tienen ellos un abogado en las páginas
websites that they have yes lawyers
web que tienen ellos sí los abogados
have a different internet than yours
tienen un internet diferente al tuyo
this guy is an idiot eh this guy is dumb
este tío es idiota eh este tío es tonto
or whatever but what are they The screenshots are not
o sea pero que están Las capturas no es
that there are the websites and blogs that
que están las páginas web y los blogs de
Tania herself published and the guy
que la propia Tania publicó y el tío te
is denying it to you Let's see
lo está negando A ver
loser I can't believe it he's the
pringado no me lo puedo creer que es el
loser of the internet he's the
pringado de internet es el
loser
pringado
God God man how handsome is that
Dios Dios tío chaval Qué guapo es eso
How handsome is that kid but but this
Qué guapo es eso chaval pero pero este
is the other one no [ __ ] man what a [ __ ]
es el otro no hostias tío vaya [__]
host this is going to be eh God of my life
[__] va a ser esto eh Dios de mi vida
man God of my life that's going to be
tío Dios de mi vida eso va a ser una
[ __ ] awesome eh man  I wish you had time
[__] pasada eh tío ojalá te diera tiempo
to do some more eh And not just those you
de hacer unas más eh Y no sola esas me
're making my teeth long
estás poniendo los dientes larguísimos
man I'll talk to you later I'm live
tío luego te hablo que estoy en directo
eh but it's [ __ ] crazy man it's
eh pero es una [__] locura tío es una
[ __ ] crazy it's [ __ ] crazy what's going
[__] locura es una [__] locura lo que va
to happen Eh family something is going to happen
a pasar Eh familia va a pasar una cosa
we are doing something that is
estamos haciendo una cosa que es una
[ __ ] crazy I will probably get it out for
[__] locura lo sacaré seguramente para
kings you'll see if it has to be a
reyes ya lo veréis si tiene que ser un
lawyer who can locate that case
abogado el que pueda localizar ese caso
how am I going to know how I know I don't
cómo lo voy a saber yo que yo sepa yo no
have a
tengo la carrera de
law degree no because what he's
derecho no porque lo que te está
telling you what's going on queen a kiss
diciendo el en qu pasa reina un beso
Thanks aunt with the data that appeared
Gracias tía con los datos que aparecían
published by the woman herself
publicados por la propia mujer se
the sentence is perfectly located Well of
localiza perfectamente la sentencia Pues
course but if she even put the name of the
claro pero si puso hasta el nombre del
judge but she even put the name of the
juez pero si puso hasta el nombre del
judge Remember Karime Remember
juez Acuérdate de Karime Acuérdate de
Karime let's see what I thought was that it
Karime a ver yo lo que pensaba era que
was a sentence for abuse which it is
era una sentencia de maltrato que lo es
also eh Because it's not only the
también eh Porque no solamente es el
issue of the minor there is also one there is
tema de la de las menor también hay una
also a sentence for abuse it is
también hay una condena por maltrato es
less than the one for abuse but there is also I
menos que la del abuso pero también la
think that for abuse  they're like 8
hay creo que la del maltrato son como 8
months or months in prison something like that I mean
meses o meses de prisión algo así O sea
they're 8 years for the abuse and a few
son 8 años por el abuso y unos cuantos
months for the mistreatment for
de meses por el maltrato por la
gender violence but but Estela without
violencia de género pero pero Estela sin
sense
sentido
none I have the hairdressing course
ninguno tengo el curso de peluquería
but I don't have a law degree
pero carrera de derecho no tengo ninguna
that to begin with second I
eso para empezar segundo yo esa historia
didn't know that story And it can be proven that I did
no la sabía Y se puede demostrar que yo
n't know that story
no sabía esa historia
of let's see if I can get the word out come on come on
de de a ver si me sale la palabra venga
come on I put it in the corner
Dale dale venga Lo ponía en la esquinita
when the lawyer did the live about
cuando abogado hizo el directo de de
that come in the corner the name the
eso ven en la esquina el nombre la
word of what and the live is gone
palabra de lo que y se te va el directo
and you can't get the word but that
y no lo consigues la palabra pero esa
sentence is anonymized like all of them
sentencia está anonimizada como todas
like all of them or is it that you didn't listen to the
como todas o es que no escuchaste al
lawyer because I didn't know that it doesn't say
abogado porque yo no lo sabía de que no
Paquito Fernández it says Don Trillo or
pone Paquito Fernández pone Don trillo o
Don
Don
Licorice he denounces Mrs. Eraser
regaliz denuncia a doña goma de borrar
because I don't know what
porque no sé qué
anonymized you have that enc just
anonimizada tienes que enc acaba de
gave away 20 family members you know that
regalar 20 miembros familia sabéis que
means that we are at 95
eso significa que estamos en 95 miembros
new members in this live 95
nuevos en este directo 95 miembros
new members in this live family thank you
nuevos en este directo familia gracias
enc from the heart eh very much very much
enc de corazón eh muchísima muchísimas
Thank you very much beautiful I hope it happens
Muchísimas gracias guapa Ojalá le toque
to Carmen who  I was asking mom
a a Carmen que lo estaba pidiendo a mamá
of and Alone I hope you get it man, comment
de y Alone Ojalá os toque tío comentar
a lot in the chat and always like
mucho en el chat y darle like siempre a
the live streams and that because I think it will
los directos y eso porque yo creo que
go by interaction I don't know does it make
que irá por interacción No lo sé tiene
sense that it would be something like that let's see what judge
sentido que sea algo así a ver qué juez
was in the case Search within
estuvo en el caso Buscar dentro de de
all the work that there is of all those
todo el trabajo que haya de todas esas
sentences that there have been in that time
sentencias que haya habido en ese tiempo
that is not an easy job and
que no es un trabajo fácil y eso no lo
Roberto Navarrete does not do that, a
hace Roberto Navarrete eso lo hace un
lawyer does Roberto Navarrete does not publish the
abogado Roberto Navarrete no publica la
sentence Roberto Navarrete what he does
sentencia Roberto Navarrete lo que hace
is when Tania says I don't know what I don't know
es cuando Tania dice no sé qué no sé
how much in her live stream she looks for and finds
cuánto en su directo busca y encuentra
the vogs and those things what
los vogs y esas cosas lo que encontró
Roberto Navarrete found not the Chain la la
Roberto Navarrete no el Chain la la los
Tania's blogs what the [ __ ] is dude the
blogs de Tania qué [__] está tío los
tran everything but you know what the worst thing is that
tran todo pero sabes qué es lo peor que
there are things that already already They even confuse you
hay cosas que ya ya Incluso te confunden
and you don't know Which ones Yes and which ones no no but there are
y no sabes Cuáles Sí y cuáles no no pero
some things that Eh there are some
hay algunas cosas que Eh hay algunas
things that they do and they say them and they
cosas que las hacen y que las dicen y
defend them because they are stupid okay But there are
las defienden por tontos vale Pero hay
other things that the one that they are
otras cosas que la que la que las están
saying on purpose that they lie
diciendo a propósito de que mienten
knowing that they lie you know let's see that
sabiendo que mienten sabes a ver que
has experience in Searching for cases in the
tiene experiencia en Buscar caso en el
past to set a precedent
pasado para Para que sienta precedente
What's it called listen to me I'm going to
Cómo se llama escúchame que te voy a
help you a little bit I see that the muscle doesn't
ayudar un poquito que veo que el músculo
work listen to me What a fool
no no lo trabaja escúchame A qué tonto
man if you see that paper, that of the
tío que si tú te ves el papel ese del
chance, that of the charge or the cherge or
chance ese del charge o del cherge o
whatever it's called, it
como se llame
has the magistrate's number and all the
ese viene el número de magistrado y todo
case number, the judge's number,
el número del caso el número del juez
that one, the judge's name and the
ese el nombre del juez y el número del
case number, all the data is published
caso todos los datos están publicados
there, that's what it's all about, let's go
ahí es que tiene mandanga es que vamos
Ah, I can't find the word they are the
Ah no me sale la palabra son las
sentences that set precedents are
sentencias que sienten precedentes son
jurisprudence creature they are the
jurisprudencia criatura son las
sentences that create precedents are not
sentencias que crean precedentes no son
jurisprudence or they make jurisprudence or
jurisprudencia o hacen jurisprudencia o
something like that, it's that I don't understand
algo de eso es que yo sí que no entiendo
eh but don't go there don't
eh pero que no vayas por ahí que no
go there because look, you're playing a
vayas por ahí que es que mira vas de
detective and I recommend that you watch the
detective y te recomiendo que veas la
series The Last Night, dear, you're missing the,
serie La última noche emor te falta los
you're missing the pieces of the puzzle, she's
te faltan las piezas del puzzle
missing the pieces of the pulle, she's not there she's
le faltan las piezas del pulle no está
half s a kiss Salomé, beautiful,
está medio s un beso Salomé guapísima
thank you very much and to María seb who has
muchísimas gracias y a María seb que ha
given away one more member one more member me
regalado un miembre más un miembre yo
piece has only given away five
más pedazo solo ha regalado cinco
more quinces there we already have more than 100
membrillos más ahí ya tenemos más de 100
new members today eh careful
miembros nuevos hoy eh cuidadito
careful eh careful
cuidadito eh cuidadito que se calienta
this is getting heated in carnica baldón has given away another
esto en carnica baldón ha regalado otro
super chat of 5 for the challenge for the
super chat de 5 para el reto para el
objective
objetivo
inito you are going How wrong you are going eh Let's see
inito vas Qué mal encamino vas eh A ver
if this is not the same because let's
este si no es el mismo porque ya a
see we start with the meatballs and
ver empezamos con los almondiga y
finish quickly with them come on
terminamos rápido con ellos venga que
the meatballs like it when I
los almondiga le gusta que le que yo le
dedicate a few minutes to them What
dedique algún minuto que otro Qué le
is albondiguilla Consuelo saying to him I don't
está diciendo albondiguilla Consuelo no
believe it no no I don't believe it I don't
me lo creo no no no me lo creo no me lo
believe it he is telling albondiguilla
creo le está diciendo albondiguilla
Consuelo I don't [ __ ] believe it It's true no
Consuelo no me lo [__] creo Es verdad no
no but with that Caro no don't [ __ ] with me don't
no pero con ese de Caro no no me jodas
[ __ ] with me no don't [ __ ] with me he is
no me jodas no no me jodas le está
telling bondig guilla to Consuelo
diciendo al bondig guilla a Consuelo
But anyway This will be super outrageous
Pero bueno Esto será super indignante
for all those who talk to this
para todos los que se hablan con este
guy no I can't [ __ ] believe it I can't
tipo no No me lo puedo [__] creer no me
but I can't [ __ ] believe it the
lo pero no me lo puedo [__] creer le
couple calls the  biga seriously a kiss
llama la pareja al biga en serio un beso
on canny Thank you very much dude I can't
en canny Muchas gracias tía no me lo
[ __ ] believe it come on you're leaving me
puedo [__] creer vamos me estáis dejando
speechless but he didn't tell him that he's
de piedra pero no le ha dicho que está
flattened by the poles So it's not
achatada por los polos Así que no es
serious Oh okay Yes yes it's true kiss
grave Ah vale Sí sí es verdad beso
Salomé gorgeous if I had told
Salomé guapísima si le hubiera dicho a
chat about the poles it would be very serious eh man
chat por los polos era gravísimo eh tío
But seriously seriously this guy hangs out
Pero en serio en serio este tío se junta
with the youtubers that hang out And
con los youtubers que se juntan Y
none of them are going to say anything to bondig
ninguno le va a decir nada al bondig
guilla but on top of that he's the bad guy of
guilla pero encima él que es el malo de
the Smurfs I do
los Pitufos sí me
love him from the moth-eaten Channel with nalina
encanta del Canal apolillado con nalina
with nalina Let's see, notify me you
con nalina A ver
haven't left me flipped out
notifica no lo me habéis dejado flipado
listen to me because I don't see your face
escúchame que yo tampoco te veo la cara
so thin either eh To the one I'm seeing more
tan fina eh A la que te estoy viendo más
closely Show me the abs
de cerca Enséñame las abdominal
okay [ __ ] what a disgusting guy
vale [__] qué asco de tipo
[Music]
[Música]
no Go with the meatball to miguillas
no V aar con la almondiga al miguillas
no
no
meatballs yes no let them eat no Elisa I do
albondiguillas sí no que coman no Elisa
n't know am marranona H but there are people
no se am marranona H pero tiene gente
who are in the chat listening to that and
que que está en el chat escuchando eso y
they think it's okay there in the chat
le parece bien tiene ahí en el chat
let's change  the menu that they eat
vamos a cambiar el menú que eso lo comen
every day a kiss Isabel Okay
todos los días un beso Isabel Bueno
let's go with the marriage to the world
vamos con con el matrimonio al mondi
Guilla well you know what you eat the one
guilla pues tú sabes lo que le comes tú
from Troy what you eat every
al de Troya lo que comes tú todos los
day you eat Loli's ass so she gives
días el culo a la Loli le comes para que
you money and she doesn't give you a penny you loser you
te dé dinero y no te da un duro pringado
are a loser that everyone gives her
que eres un pringado que le da todo el
except you because you're stupid that you
mundo menos a ti que eres tonto que
have audios where
tienes hay audios que te están diciendo
they are telling you that she doesn't have cancer and you telling her that you cover her up to defend her trust you what you eat and why I don't want to tell you what you eat to me there we have them look beauty in its
ahí las tenemos mir belleza en estado
purest form don't get
puro no te vayas a
excited this is beauty in its purest form
emocionar esto es belleza en estado puro
Look who was talking man but he's
Mira quién fue hablar tío pero está
talking about
hablando de
beauty but he's talking about beauty man
bellez pero que está hablando de bellez
man that I've seen get a strike for
tío tío que yo he visto poner strike por
calling someone a croquette How the [ __ ] does
llamar a alguien croqueta Cómo [__]
this have an audience and you know what I'm
esto tiene un público e sabes lo que te
telling you be it's not that it doesn't add up or
digo sea es que no es que no me cuadra o
rather I didn't expect this do you think he's
sea yo esto no lo esperaba me cree que
saying it for something else I don't know
lo está diendo por otra cosa no sé
okay I'm younger than you
vale Yo soy más joven que tú
by pay well I am I am my husband from
por paga pues lo soy lo soy mi marido de
the brown ones of  my husband said that one
las pardas de mi marido eso decía una
that they gave him a bunch of millions
que le dieron un montón de millones por
because the husband died in a
porque el marido murió en accidente de
car accident he was hit by a van for the
coche lo arrolló una furgoneta para
poor man's rest and the t was renovated
descanso del pobre y se reformó la t el
his Mourning was to reform the house and he
Duelo suyo fue reformarse la casa y
said these pair
decía estas par
How good that is man but no they are
Qué bueno eso tío pero no a me están
sending me a retweet hands clapping hands clapping hands clapping hands clapping hands clapping face
mandando un retweet manos aplaudiendo
throwing a kiss face throwing a kiss face throwing a kiss a
lanzando un beso cara lanzando un beso
kiss mini
cara lanzando un beso un beso mini
Maleficent the ard of Troy today he
Maléfica el ard de Troya hoy mismo ha
retweeted okay
retuiteado vale
posts accusing the
publicaciones acusando de gordofobia al
black man from vox of fatphobia whom we have criticized
negro de vox al que hemos criticado
before for the same thing you know well today today
antes por lo mismo sabes pues hoy mismo
today he retweeted tweet
hoy mismo hoy mismo ha retuiteado tweet
with which I am completely in
con lo que estoy Completamente de
agreement defending lal chus and
acuerdo defendiendo a a lal chus y
while you are retweeting that the the
mientras que estás retuiteado eso el el
head knee is there Calling
el cabez rodilla está ahí Llamando al
a marriage a biga man they
biga a un matrimonio tío es que no
have no coherence they have no
tienen coherencia no tienen no tiene
sense it is worth absolutely nothing man
sentido no vale absolutamente nada tío
they are rabble nothing of what he says
son gentusa no vale nada de lo que diga
eh Nothing of what he defends is
eh No vale nada de lo que defienda no
worth nothing of  what I criticize is
vale nada de lo que critique no vale
worthless dude they have no principles they have no
nada tío no tienen principio no tienen
values ​​they have nothing dude
valores no tienen nada tío
But if you tell me what consolation
Pero si tú me dices a mí que consuelo le
is insulting him in the same
está insultando a en el mismo
tone a kiss enc guapa Thank you very much
tono un beso enc guapa Muchísimas
enc damn damn enc well what a
gracias enc [__] [__] enc pues vaya
push you just gave us eh Look
empujón que nos acabas de dar eh Mira
so that people make fun of me
para que la gente vacile de mi
lords of my brand No I'm
señoreros de mi marillo No yo al mío lo
going to embalm mine to have it here all
voy a embalsamar para tenerlo aquí todo
day bring really with the death that
el día bring de verdad con la muerta que
the poor guy has had really you have to be
ha tenido el pobre de verdad hay que ser
bad people But about that You know a lot about
mala gente Pero de eso Tú sabes mucho de
being bad people it shouldn't
ser mala gente a ti no te tiene que
surprise you you would do worse things
sorprender eso tú harías peores cosas
for sure You are the bad person on
seguro Tú sí que eres mala gente en
these walls show off the skin of my
estas paredes luce el pellejo de mi
Maria Hello Cala Blanca very good evening
María Hola cala Blanca muy buenas noches
Greetings to all the people who are
Un saludo a toda la gente que está
coming in ma Julieta very
entrando ma Julieta muy
good
buenas
Lisa and Maria Rosabel Ciancio very good
lisa y María rosabel ciancio muy buenas
evening you are the couple of the
noches son pareja del
year let's listen to Guilla Sacra there are
año vamos a escuchar guilla Sacra hay
a few more scoundrels and I know what I'm
unos cuantos más sinvergüenzas y sé lo
saying be careful with the stubbornness he
que me digo cuid con la cabezota que
has and he doesn't remember what he says I
tiene y no se acuerda de lo que dice a
love him  he starts talking she
mí me encanta él empieza a hablar ella
steps on him He keeps talking they step on each
le pisa Él sigue hablando se pisan uno
other this is a happy marriage Of
al otro esto el matrimonio feliz Pues
course a happy marriage let's see if you're
claro el matrimonio feliz a ver si te
going to think that we live in a
vas a pensar tú que vivimos en una
dictatorship Well he talks I talk what is
dictadura Pues él habla hablo yo lo
normal of course we step on each other Well he wants to say
normal claro nos pisamos Pues él quiere
I want to say we're not going to be
decir yo quiero decir no vamos a estar
there alone moth-eaten ap thumb how
ahí solos apolillados ap pulgar como
are you you my goodness You really have such
estás tú tú madre mía Tú sí que tienes
happiness on that channel my goodness it
una felicidad en ese canal madre mía
seems like I'm watching a channel from the
parece que esty viendo un canal de los
80s in
años 80 en color
sepia it seems like I'm watching a
sepia es que pare que esté viendo un
channel in sepia
canal en color sepia madre
my goodness well we continue we continue because it's that
mía bueno seguimos seguimos porque es
if I start to follow her This is
que como empiece a la sigo Esta es
friend one to friend two remember that one
almiga uno al miga dos se acuerda ese
has the most evil of the entire platform that that's the
tiene más maldad de toda la plataforma
great truth that my
eso esa es la la gran verdad que dice mi
husband says Carmen from October just
marido Carmen de octubre acaba de
gave away another 20 members how do you see it
regalar otros 20 miembros cómo lo ves
Anika let's see Anika I am I am I am feeling
anika a ver anika yo estoy estoy estoy
sleepy eh today I am making
con sueñecito eh hoy estoy haciendo aquí
the effort here to be here for a while and
el esfuerzo para estar aquí un ratillo y
then I'm going to go to the kids' room eh
luego me vo ir para la chavalería eh
but Anika yesterday convinced the kids about the
pero anika ayer convenció a los chavales
members issue okay with an audio
del tema miembros vale con un audio
Anika me  you have to send look at carni
anika me tienes que mandar mira en carni
has given away another five anik you have to
ha regalado otros cinco anik me tienes
send me an audio because I can't anymore I
que mandar un audio tú porque yo ya no
'm exhausted And on top of that I can't stop
puedo estoy agotado Y encima no paro de
hearing nonsense here anika I need
escuchar tonterías aquí anika Necesito
an audio with which you who also get
un audio con el que tú que además se
closer to you the gentlemen eria eh
acercan más a ti la señoreros ería eh
with which you convince the
con el que tú convenzas a la
gentlemen because I can see you there
señoreros porque te estoy viendo ahí
a little indignant in the chat okay
como un poco indignada en el chat vale
but of course Don't tell the
pero claro No le vayas a decir a la
gentlemen to the kids yesterday Ana yesterday
señoreros a la chavalería ayer Ana ayer
told her told the kids Javi to us
le dijo le dijo a la chavalería Javi nos
Javi Javi they are We are their
lo Javi Javi son Nosotros somos sus
joints I don't know why she said that but that's what she
porros no sé por qué dijo eso pero eso
said I mean anika said yesterday to the
dijo o sea anika dijo ayer a la
kids to convince him to
chavalería para convencerlo de que
give members We are their joints they
dieran miembro Nosotros somos sus porros
told the kids that don't tell him
a los chavales le dijeron eso no le
and the kids gave away
vayas a decir y los chavales regalaron
1200 members Don't tell that to
1200 miembros No le vayas a decir eso a
the
la
gentlemen super challenge chat a kiss
señoreros super chat del reto un beso
beautiful you are the worst on the entire
guapa eres el más malo de toda la
platform the evil gene you
plataforma el gen de la maldad lo lo has
created it bad bad is the word eh you
creado tú malo malo es la palabra eh lo
have it internalized there you are evil
tienes ahí interiorizado eres la maldad
in a state  pure You're bad bad bad bad It
en estado puro Eres malo malo malo malo
's bad bad and not for what you're
Es malo mal y no por lo que estás
doing saying about me that's the
haciendo diciendo de mí que es lo de
least of it pradillo now I'll tell you
menos pradillo ahora te cuento El Por
Why he says for me that I'm the one who
qué dice por mí que yo soy el que más
has the most evil what is that you don't
maldad tiene a mí lo que es que no me
scare me at all No if I don't
dais miedo ninguno No si yo miedo no te
have to give you fear good good bu let's see fear
tengo que dar bueno bueno bu a ver miedo
fear when I entered the chapar of
miedo cuando yo entré en el chapar de
heel of bat and tell him to come he
talón de bate y decirle que viniera le
got one he got a little kick there in him in the
entró una le entró un un cocillo ahí en
underwear that I don't know I have to
el en el calzón que no sé yo hay que
tell you the one who's
decirte al de
lying there it got you let's go you shook
[__] ahí te entró vamos te tembló
even your bangs you can see the expression on your
hasta el flequillo se ve la expresión de
face that he's bad man son but let's
la cara que es malo hombre hijo pero a
see this guy He's bad I don't think it's
ver que este tío Es malo no creo yo que
a secret here either no what I
sea tampoco un secreto aquí no lo que te
have to give you is that you ignore me I
tengo que dar es que me ignores miedo
have to give you no fear you
ninguno te tengo que dar yo a ti me me
give me between disgust
dais entre asquito
yes from disgust everything
sí a partir de asquito todo lo que
you want eh From disgust and why And why do you
quieras eh A partir de asco y para qué Y
name me why do you expose me
para qué me nombras para qué me expones
why am I there
para qué estoy ahí
ignore me Why have you been talking about me for more than a year that I
ignórame Para qué llevas más de un año
can get the
hablando de mí que te puedo sacar los
clips ignore me How I did with you
clips ignórame Cómo hecho yo contigo
During this time until you've screwed up
Durante este tiempo hasta que has metido
but well screwed up already to the point of
la gamba pero bien metida ya hasta hasta
laziness of talking about you
pereza de de hablar de vosotros
answering you laziness of seeing you in
responderos pereza de ha verte a ti en
sepia laziness of seeing you in
color sepia pereza de ha verte a ti en
sepia that I understand that the image
color sepia que entiendo que la imagen
of your channel has to be that to give
de tu canal tiene que ser esa para dar
the pity that you want to give so that they go
la pena que queréis dar para que vayan
releasing memberships and memberships and bizum
soltando membresías y membresías y bizum
and that they pay the electricity and that they pay this and
y que paguen la luz y que paguen esto y
the dog's gummies and I don't know how much
las gominolas del perro y no sé cuánto
I only the G not the
yo solo las G no la del
dog's I can understand that it's a whole
perro puedo entender que es toda una
aesthetic organized so that they go
estética organizada para que te vayan
releasing you what does boss say if you want to
soltando que dice jefe si quieres
hallucinate completely Put the video and
alucinar del todo Pon el vídeo y me
tell me what you think But what video what
cuentas qué te parece Pero qué vídeo qué
video do you want me to put come on Yes, [ __ ] [ __ ]
vídeo quiere que ponga vamos Eso sí
the kids are only 101 You
[__] [__] la chavalería solo 101 Ya
better close it and let's go to the series grandpa they do
mejor cierra y vámonos al serie abuelo
n't appreciate you here it's nothing personal
aquí no te aprecian no es nada personal
Mr. Eria but I even told
señor eria pero hasta le comenté a
wizard and he says they don't deserve it damn [ __ ]
wizard y dice que no lo merecen ostia
[ __ ] [ __ ] what a bastard guy I mean it
ostia ostia ostia qué cabrón tío O sea
's nothing personal on top of that  He comes with
no es nada personal encima viene con
a lot of education eh That That's my
mucha educación eh Esa Esa es mi
kids what the education that I have
chavalería lo que la educación que yo le
taught my kids That's the
he enseñado a mis chavales Esa es la
education that I have taught my
educación que yo le he enseñado a mis
kids has entered here with a lot of
chavales ha entrado aquí con mucho
respect does not give super chat okay he gives a
respeto no da super chat vale él da un
euro there in the link that in
euro ahí en en lo del enlace ese de en
the description you have it in case you
la descripción lo tenéis por si alguna
ever want to talk there that
vez queréis hablar por ahí que te
allows you the longest text okay but with
permite el texto más largo vale pero con
all the [ __ ] nerve he gives you a joke let's
toda la [__] cara os mete una vacilada a
see wow let's see wow they have given 126
ver wale a ver wale han dado 126
members not bad no Apart I tell you one
miembros nada mal no Aparte te digo una
thing eh the members of the members
cosa eh los miembros de los los miembros
of the
de la
gentlemen Expensive that the kids that
señoreros Caro que los de la chavalería
you are all Latin Americans
que ustedes sois todos latinoamericanos
of that let's see they give you 1000 members and maybe they have
de eso a ver te regalan 1000 miembros y
spent
y a lo mejor se han gastado
3 But how does the scoundrel rogue come
3 Pero cómo viene El sinvergüenza picaro
eh Let's see I'll see if Anica I'll see if
eh A ver voy a ver si Anica voy a ver si
Anika has sent an audio okay it's
anika ha mandado un audio vale qu da
lazy because what you are looking for that you have been
pereza porque lo que buscáis que lleváis
looking for my mouth for months looking for my
ya buscándome la boca meses buscándome
mouth is that  I pay attention to you but but you
la boca es que os haga casito pero pero
started to name me you were
que empezaste a nombrarme tú tú fuiste
the first one who named me you were the
el primero que me nombraste tú fuiste el
first one who gave your phone number to
primero que le pasaste tu teléfono a una
someone so that they could give it to me to keep
persona para que me lo pasara para estar
in touch with me and I didn't even register it
en contacto conmigo y ni me lo registré
on my cell phone if you are unregistered I
en el móvil si estáis sin registrar lo
ignored it and I completely ignored what are you
ignoré y pasé olímpicamente qué me estás
telling me what are you telling me that today you have
contando qué me estás contando que hoy
achieved it today we have
lo habéis conseguido hoy lo hemos
achieved it for several days because you haven't
conseguido varios días porque no nos has
let us For a year eh No no no they don't
dejado Durante un año eh No no no no
distinguish where it is in their group because
distinguen dónde es en su grupo porque
they are a group they are part of a
ellos sí son un grupo forman parte de un
group a criminal gang well Valencia
grupo una banda criminala pues Valencia
the group that I make with my moderators and
el grupo que hago con mis moderadoras y
my husband will refer you to that group it can't
mi marido te referirá a ese grupo no
be yes I'm not telling you no and
puede ser que sí No te digo que no y
I'm sure it is no it's that
segurísimo que sí no es
or misol you're out
que o misol otra vez estás por
there again Valencia Valencia that has gone through
ahí Valencia Valencia que ha pasado por
the flight through all of our channels and in the
el vuelo por todos nuestros canales y al
end it ends up in the morraya channels this
final acaba en los canales morraya esto
these morraya channels that Samuel Peña
estos canales morraya que Samuel Peña
But these are
Pero estos son
kids these are kids Jai you
chavales estos son chavales Jai no
shouldn't be in the kids now let's
deberías estar en la chavalería ahora a
see Samuel now I'm going or so of course it's that
ver Samuel ahora voy o sea claro es que
I have the live stream of the
tengo programado el directo de la
kids scheduled I had it scheduled for 12
chavalería lo tenía programado a las 12
o'clock, I'm a little late okay say it
men vo ha llegado un poco tarde vale
there in the chat to you because the
dilo por allí por el chat a tien que el
trolls have a face like gazpachuelo I
[__] tiene cara de gazpachuelo he
hung up Oh my God of my life Hey but
cortado Ay Dios mío de mi vida Oye pero
please the kids and put them in the
por favor la chavalería y ponerles en el
chat there because I'm going to take a little while because I'm going to
chat allí que voy a tardar un poquillo
take a little while 15
que voy a tardar un poquillo 15
minutes but yes, the
minutillos pero si está está la
gentlemen are there members sites and others just like
señoreros miembre sitos y demás igual
you look at carni just
que ustedes mira en carni acaba de
gave away another five the only thing they
regalar otros cinco de lo único que
live on is criticizing the rest of us and
viven es de de criticarnos a los demás y
but have you seen my
de pero os habéis visto vosotros yo qué
nerve I mean bring up a topic I sent you an
morro o sea saca un tema te envié un
audio Javi you sent me an audio I'm going to wait until
audio Javi me enviaste un audio voy en
Anica's audio
lo que lle el audio de Anica yo
arrives I only okay until
solamente okay en lo que llegue el audio
Anica's audio arrives I only have a question
de Anica yo solamente tengo una pregunta
for the gentlemen the
para la señoreros la
gentlemen Do you think
señoreros Creen ustedes que vale el
Javi's time is worth your time as an
tiempo de Javi el tiempo de ustedes como
audience and the suffering of having to
audiencia y el sufrimiento de tener que
listen to the trolls talk like that
estar escuchando al [__] hablar de esa
about a lady like Consuelo
manera de una dama Como lo es Consuelo
just answer the question with
simplemente respondan a la pregunta con
this  memberships and with super chats And with
este membresías y con super chats Y con
everything you have on hand it works and is worth it
todo lo que tengan a la mano sale y vale
ladies Well go ahead Let's go with that Hey
señoras Pues dale Vámonos con eso Oye
with Vincente miime Hey with Vincente miim it's
con vincente miime Oye con vincente miim
understood from you eh How among the
de ustedes se entendé eh Cómo entre la
gentlemen the kids like pecking Javi
señoreros los chavales como picando Javi
Let's go to the kids these people don't
Vámonos a la chavalería esta gente no te
give you members I don't know I don't know how much and
dan miembros no sé no sé cuánto y llega
Karime arrives and says lady I don't know what there are already
Karime y dice señora no sé qué ya hay
100 people waiting for you grandpa I'm coming
100 personas esperándote abuelo Ya voy
man put it in the chat it's going to take me
tío ponerle en el chat que voy a tardar
15 minutes smoke a joint no no a joint
15 minutillos fumar un porrete no no un
no a joint no very good night
porro no un porro no muy buenas noches
ladies and gentlemen I was at the live show where
señoreros estuve en el directo en donde
100 members were donated it was a
se donó 100 miembros fue una noche
magical night but at the same time very outrageous to hear
mágica pero a la vez muy indignante oír
many people from the chavería say that
a mucha gente de la chavería decir que
the lordship is incapable of donating
la señoría es incapaz de donar ni
even half of the members we are going to
siquiera la mitad de miembros vamos a
allow some kids to tell us that
permitir que unos chavales nos digan eso
you ladies that we can donate a
ustedes señoras que podemos donar un
member each that we are we beat them in
miembro cada una que somos le ganamos en
majority and and we are going to allow them to
mayoría y y vamos a permitir que ellos
destroy us in that way
nos echen por tierra de esa forma
let's demonstrate  a kiss Adrian the salsería
demostremos un beso Adrián la salsería
commands
manda
H man I'm going I'm going to see what
de H tío voy voy a ver lo que dice
Consuelo says Wait up kids we are
Consuelo Espérate niñatos que
the [ __ ] best we are the
somos la [__] [__] que somos las
best the ladies we are the ones who
mejores que las señoras somos las que
dominate Javi Oliveira's channels
dominamos los canales de Javi oliveira
So come on
Así que venga
ladies one each so a kiss to
señoras uno cada uno así que un beso a
everyone and let's show who we are the
todos y demostremos quiénes Somos la
gentlemen
señoreros
[Laughter]
[Risas]
where you have to but let's see half of them are
donde tienen que pero a ver la mitad
not in love that in love Let's see it's
tampoco enamorada que enamorada A ver es
clear what happened yesterday what happened
que claro es que lo de ayer es que lo de
yesterday at the salsería was very long it's that
ayer en la salsería fue muy tocho es que
Anik says even if it's half It's that
dice anik aunque sea la mitad Es que la
half goes it's complicated it's that half
mitad va está complicado es que la mitad
are 600 Anica half of them are not either eh Let's see they
son 600 Anica la mitad tampoco eh A ver
told me they
me han dicho que pongan me han dicho me
told me on WhatsApp to put it on
han dicho por WhatsApp que ponga a
from this minute eh that we have already
partir de este minuto eh que ya hemos
heard a bit of aar of Troy
escuchado un poco aar de Troya faltando
disrespecting and all that but that we put it on
al respeto y todo eso pero que pongamos
from this minute they told me on
a partir de este minuto me han dicho por
WhatsApp I don't know why we're going to see two
WhatsApp no sé por qué vamos a ver dos
turds from the same
cagarruta de la misma
goat two turds from the same goat two turds from
cabra dos cagarrutas de la misma cabra
the same goat he
dos cagarrutas de la misma cabra les
calls them there  there's my meat one member
llama ahí está mi carni un un miembro
each if I don't ask for more eh I don't
cada uno si yo tampoco pido más eh yo no
want to give away 1000 members like
quiero que me regalé 1000 miembros como
these people but one member each and
a esta gente pero un miembro cada uno y
and and we eat it the kids
y y nos lo comemos a los chavales que se
[ __ ] off there waiting for the live
jodan allí esperando que está el directo
program well they have time they have
programa bueno tienen tiempo tienen
a lot more life ahead of them damn they
tienen mucha más vida por delante [__]
are young let them shower or something
son jóvenes que se duchen o algo de
meanwhile
mientras
say yes in canny look and my Karim
di que sí en canny mira y mi Karim me
has also given me a member say yes
también ha regalado un miembro di que sí
Look Karim has given me another member yes yes yes yes yes that
Mira Karim me ha regalado otro miembro
I'll
más que sí que sí que sí que sí que yo
watch it eh one member each and let them
lo veo eh un miembro cada uno y que se
stay there waiting for the ass for a
queden allí esperando el por culo un
while damn Look p has given away another one [ __ ]
rato [__] Mira p ha regalado otro [__]
Guillermo says one year of the best
ya Guillermo dice un año del mejor
government in history Guillermo but
gobierno de la historia Guillermo pero
Pedro Sánchez you don't mean no
Pedro Sánchez no te refieres no
Guillermo Ah okay long live freedom
Guillermo Ah vale viva la libertad
damn okay he's with my law Hello
[__] vale que está con mi ley Hola
María Rey very good evening Yana Isabel let's
María Rey muy buenas noches yana Isabel
see maybe I forgot something because I counted let's
a ver igual me olvidado algo porque cont
see if Ah Look at this this here How
a ver si lo Ah Mira esto esto aquí Cómo
what this look what do you think how Anica
qué esto mira qué os parece cómo Anica
Anica has given away another one very well because
Anica ha regalado otro muy bien porque
you have to lead by example
tienes que predicar con el ejemplo
exactly how you can win  la la life
exactamente cómo podes ganar la la vida
Doing striptease Look look look look look it's that
Haciendo striptis Mira mira mira mira
I don't have to earn a
mira es que yo no me tengo que ganar la
living it's that you haven't realized
vida es que tú no te has enterado
yet that I don't need to work
todavía que no necesito trabajar
doing striptease I'm
haciendo striptis Yo me estoy quedando
dying with him with the art of Troy eh for
muerto con el con el ar de Troya eh xa
another member if I do them I
otro miembre sillo si se los hago se los
do them to my husband chirping you have
hago a mi marido me chiando tú tienes a
someone to do it to I think not but
quien hacérselo yo creo que no pero de
anyways tinker bell another Hey I
todas maneras campanilla otro Oye me
'm dying with this
estoy quedando muerto con esto no
we're not commenting on the members
estamos comentando lo de los miembros
But this seems too
Pero esto nos está pareciendo demasiado
strong vomitous in fact it
fuerte vomitivo de hecho nos está
seems vomitous to us work it
pareciendo vomitivo trabájalo
work it
trabájalo
the top and it doesn't fall you're stuck
la peonza y no se cae estáis agarrada
like a tick in holding on like ticks hold on like
como una garrapata en agarrar como las
ticks like you hold on to Loli
garrapatas como tú te agarras a Loli
so she lets you
para que te
go
suelte
eh Clara you're a little freaked because
eh Clara estás un poquito mosca porque
the money is going to Maite another member
se va el dinero para Maite otro miembro
ole that's what I wanted one each one
ole eso es lo que yo quería uno cada uno
each side eh man I'm freaking out
uno cada uno lado eh tío estoy flipando
my experience already Hello more Juli such a
mi experiencia ya Hola más Juli tal
bquilla because they are round or for  another
bquilla porque son redonditos o por otro
guy you have to keep in mind that
tío que tenéis que tener en cuenta que
these riffraff got happy and
estas gentusa se han alegrado y se han
started making fun of a sentence of mine
puesto a burlarse de una sentencia mía
because I insulted another youtuber and
porque yo insulté a otro youtuber y a
another youtuber warse warse gave away 50
otra youtuber warse warse ha regalado 50
señoreros that he hit you The warse but the warse
señoreros que os ha pegado El warse pero
but the warse is not the
el warse pero el warse no es de la
most host lord but warse 50 warse it is
señoreros más [__] pero warse 50 warse
not necessary I do not want to give away
no hace falta No quiero que regalé
bestialities each one separately I
bestialidades cada uno por separado
want each person to give one
quiero que cada una persona regale uno
to demonstrate power it is not that yes dude I mean
para demostrar el poder no es que sí tío
Lili is telling me says this
O sea me lo está diciendo Lili dice este
is the one who was scandalized and has and has
es el que se escandalizaba y se ha y se
joined to sink you repeating your
ha unido para hundirte repitiendo tu
clim I [ __ ] with the forera dude they
clim me teote con la forera tío que se
start taking my clim of the year I do not know
ponen a [__] clim mío del año no sé
how much of the year we are I do not know how much and that I
cuánto vamos del año no sé cuánto y que
would repeat again today because
volvería a repetir a día de hoy porque
in the clicks they put I am
en los clicks que ponen me estoy
messing with the foreras and with
metiendo con con las foreras y con
riffraff that had even messed with
gentusa que se habían metido hasta con
Lorena you understand but this one He gets
Lorena me entiendes pero que este Se
together with that friend Joan Plana who
junta con la amiga esa de Joan plana que
says that  is a lawyer this one He meets with
dice que es abogada este Se junta con
Tania this one meets you know says
con la Tania este se junta sabes dice
Rena every 1 50 best man every 1 50 it
Rena cada 1 50 mejor hombre cada 1 50
would be [ __ ] crazy but I don't think it's
sería una [__] locura pero no creo que
possible Rena do you understand me or
sea posible Rena me entiendes o sea O
rather I mean imagine
sea imaginaros
that next year I have another trial
que el año que viene tengo otro juicio
next year I have another trial
el año que viene yo tengo otro juicio
eh I don't know if you know because of course since
eh No sé si lo sabéis porque claro como
Tania is on sick leave she won't
ahora Tania está de baja pues no os
have informed you but the same ones as
habrá informado pero las mismas de
always filed another lawsuit against me
siempre a mí me pusieron otra demanda el
last year the lawsuit is about
año pasado que la demanda trata
that Mario tiberia a youtuber
de de que el Mario tiberia un youtuber
who is high and who is crazed
que está fumados y que está colgado me
made me a guest on you know a guest is
hizo un guest en you know un guest es
a call Okay and and he started insulting
una llamada Vale y y se puso en insultar
Miare and her mother I think Miare
a miare y a su madre Creo que a miare
more than her mother in that case okay the
más que a su madre en ese caso vale la
lawsuit was filed by Miare because at
demanda la puso solo miare porque en
that moment the mother We
aquel momento la madre Ya la ya la
had already caught her insulting me on the
habíamos trincado insultándome en
internet and such and she didn't take any risks but
internet y tal Y no se arriesgó pero la
the lawsuit is mainly about that
la demanda trata sobre todo sobre que
Marius insulted her it's true that he said some
marius la insultó que verdad que le dijo
very ugly things to her okay but I took the
cosas muy fea vale pero yo cogí el
live stream running it I deleted it from my
directo corriendo lo lo lo eliminé de mi
guz because when it's a guest of you
guz porque cuando es un guest de you
know they're like calls on both profiles
know son como llamadas en ambos perfiles
Okay and and I deleted it running I
Vale y y lo eliminé corriendo le pedí
apologized and that's not it and Peter okay a
disculpas y eso no lo y Peter vale un
click of that is a click what they
click de eso es un click lo que ellas
put in that lawsuit eh it's a click from
ponen en esa demanda eh es un click de
2019 okay
2019 vale
eem instead of suing Marius they
eem en vez de demandar a marius me
sue me okay I understand that to
demandan a mí vale entiendo que para
then make headlines in faca and those
luego sacar titulares en faca y esas
things because if not it doesn't have any other meaning
cosas porque si no no tiene otro sentido
and to say that they were right about something Not
y para decir que tenían razón en algo No
clear eh To me that they're not going to come to me If
claro eh A mí que no me vaya a venir Si
I lose that lawsuit none of these to
yo pierdo esa demanda ninguno de estos a
tell me anything eh I say I eh I say I
decirme nada eh digo yo eh digo yo eh
say that that none of these are going to come to me to
digo yo que que que a mí no me vayan a
tell me anything
venir ninguno de estos a decirme nada
but but none of these And none of
pero pero ninguno de estos Y ninguno de
those who get together with this one I don't say I eh I
los que se juntan con este no digo yo eh
say I eh I don't know how you see it eh of
digo yo eh No sé cómo lo veis ustedes eh
course what the [ __ ] are these people going to tell you for a
claro qué [__] [__] te van a decir
reason because they are round
esta gente motivo porque son redonditos
Ah yes, the way it says it if it's a
Ah si es que la forma los dice si es una
ball with a glob a ball with a
bola con un pegote una bola con un
glob let's say that you don't tell me in
pegote vamos que tú a mí de cuerpo
full body either  stand up in the channel
entero tampoco ponte de pie en el canal
boy show off that beer belly of
muchacho enseña esa barriguita cervecera
yours you tell me Come on man and
que tienes tú decí a mí Anda hombre y
this What is this woman doing that being black?
esto Qué es que de nigras esta mujer que
Well if this woman
está haciendo eso pues si esta mujer
is overweight and her dream is to do
tiene sobrepeso y su ilusión es hacer
that, where's the problem? Where's the
eso donde está el problema Dónde está el
problem with people having dreams? I
problema de que la gente tenga ilusiones
'm freaking out fatphobic you're
yo estoy flipando gordofobico que eres
a [ __ ] fatphobic no no man but
un puñetero gordofobico no no tío pero
Hol Ho another Look look look at her look at
que Hol Ho otro Mira mira mira ella mira
her look at her Ho is doing things
ella mira ella Ho está rando cosas
against fatphobia and obviously
contra la gordofobia y evidentemente
as Elton gets in he grows up here
como entra Elton se crece aquí el
this loser grows up on the strip bars
pringao este se crece en las barras de
eh you can do it you've visited many
eh podes hacerlo tú has visitado muchas
strip bars I'm freaking out for you for
barras de striptis estoy flipando tú por
me no you have visited them to know
yo no tú las has visitado para saber
so much freaking out Duo one up the other
tanto flipando Dúo uno arriba el otro
down the other down and the other up
abajo el otro abajo y el otro arriba
Look, I'm going to tell you something I have
Mira te voy a decir una cosa Yo tengo
someone to put myself with one down the other up the
con quien ponerme uno abajo el otro
other up the other down I
arriba el otro arriba el otro abajo yo
have someone to put myself with do the
tengo con quien ponerme hacer el
helicopter do the wheelbarrow let's do whatever
helicóptero hacer la carretilla vamos lo
we want because thank God we
que nos d la gana porque gracias a Dios
can but Ho you have to do it
podemos pero Ho tú tienes con hacerlo
How bad is loneliness look there's a
Qué mala es la soledad mir hay
mat  so that you both rod
colchoneta para que rodis los dos
pure wonder pure wonder Look at the
maravilla pura maravilla pura Mira la
other one behind how she pees listen to me that
otra de atrás cómo se mea escúchame que
for you to find these videos that are the ones
para tú encontrar estos vídeos que es
you search for on the internet because
los que buscas tú por internet porque a
these videos do not appear for me eh you will have to
mí estos vídeos no me salen eh habrá que
see the Google search engine of your
ver el Buscador de Google de tu
browser the browsing history I would
navegador el historial de navegación Me
like to see the browsing history
gustaría ver el historial de navegación
of your Google kid so that
de tu Google chaval para que te salgan
these videos appear But what is it that you are
estos vídeos Pero qué es lo que tú
looking for then put these things my goodness
buscas poner luego estas cosas madre mía
But come on what you do is denigrate
Pero vamos que lo que haces es denigrar
the one who is there you are not
a la que está ahí a mí no me estás
denigrating me Eh I can assure you And you
denigrando Eh ya te lo puedo asegurar Y
are staying because of course watching
estás quedando tú porque claro viendo
This video that is
Este vídeo que ya es
enough listen to me More than anything because
suficiente escúchame Más que nada porque
the poor woman who is there
la pobre mujer que está ahí dando
hanging around is not to blame for
vueltas tampoco tiene culpa de que tú
what you have done but
hayas hecho lo que has hecho pero
listen to me your search engine of your Google history
escuchame el buscador tuyo del historial
of going there so that
tuyo de de pasar ahí para que te salgan
these videos appear And it is degrading that people
esos vídeos Y es denigrante que la gente
according to you eh For what you are doing it
según tú eh Por lo que estás haciendo
has to be degrading no
tiene que ser denigrante no
eh And they do not remove the channel no
eh Y a este no le quitan el canal no
María José hairs on him no he no He is  the
María José pelos a él no él no Él es el
cult of
culto de
YouTube listen to me and that women
YouTube escúchame y que las mujeres
do striptease or have the need to
hagan striptis o tengan la necesidad de
work as dancers in those places
trabajar como bailarinas en esos sitios
for you That's
para ti
how it is you don't take out the nigras and
Eso es así no las sacas las de nigras y
others
demás
no incredible but come on I would like to see I would
no increíble pero vamos que me gustaría
like to see your
ver Me gustaría ver tu historial de
devilish search history the
búsqueda diabólica el historial de
search history would have to be that of this
búsqueda tendría que ser el de este
man don't see
hombre no veas
no to take out these
no para sacar estos
videos well the woman man has his merit
vídeos pues tiene su mérito la mujer
more merit than the gas eh
hombre más mérito que las del gas eh
listen to me they do that in a
escúchame que eso lo hacen en en modo de
mocking way because he does it in mocking way
burla porque él lo hace en modo de burla
but a featherweight can hold up anywhere
pero un peso pluma aguanta en cualquier
the merit is the one who doesn't have a
lado el mérito es la que no tiene peso
featherweight or the one who doesn't have a featherweight and
pluma o el que no tiene peso pluma y
does that let's see if he's so thin
hace eso a ver si tan delgado que está
he has the balls to do that at you have this one
él tiene narices hacer eso at tenés este
doesn't have the balls to do anything how heavy he
no tiene narices a nada qu heavy me ha
seemed to me Consuelo was him before
parecido Consuelo era él antes de
going bald that's why you can't find him
quedarse calvo por eso no lo encuentras
how strong he seemed to me eh how strong
qué fuerte me ha parecido eh qué fuerte
everything seemed to me Eh This would
me ha parecido todo Eh Esto se
end if they didn't give him publicity already
terminaría si no le dieran publicidad ya
Oscar but it's not only that they
Óscar pero es que él no solamente es que
give him publicity it's that he collaborates with
le den publicidad es que él colabora con
a lot of channels too now you know Of course  He
un montón de canales también ahora sabes
gets paid by those like
Claro que le dan bola los que son como
him but I'll tell you one thing eh Let's see if
él pero yo os digo una cosa eh A ver si
I can explain it to you and you
soy capaz de explicaros lo y me
understand me okay I'm going I'm running over
entendéis vale voy Voy corriendo para
there I'm running over there they're
allá voy corriendo para allá me están
scolding me eh luare who is the head of
riñendo eh luare que es el jefe de
content is scolding me Okay
contenidos me está riñendo Vale
and luares and Lili are the heads of
e luares y Lili son los jefes de
content
contenido
and I'm saying one thing about this now
que yo digo una cosa respecto a esto ya
with this we're going for today okay No, it's not over eh I
con esto nos vamos por hoy vale No no se
mean we're going to the salsería
acaba eh o sea nos vamos a la salsería
immediately there's a raid Okay when
inmediatamente hay una raide Vale cuando
when I kiss here the live
cuando chape yo aquí el directo os va a
the pum button will appear on the screen and we
aparecer en pantalla el botón pum y
enter the salsería where we have a lot of
entramos en la salsería que allí tenemos
gossip there too okay but I'm
tela de cotilleo también vale pero yo
saying one thing here let's see if you don't
aquí digo una cosa a ver si no me
misunderstand me and you all understand okay
malinterpretar y me entendéis todos vale
for me when a person makes this
para mí cuando una persona hace este
type of comment he's not humiliating in
tipo de comentario no Está humillando en
this case Consuelo I mean the one who's
este caso a Consuelo o sea el que se
humiliating himself is him let me explain I mean
Está humillando es él me explico o sea
ard de Troya with those comments he's
ard de Troya con esos comentarios está
trying to make Consuelo look bad I mean
intentando dejar mala Consuelo O sea
humiliate her I'm not messing with you no but it's that
humillarla no me meto contigo no pero es
you're offending yourself  ar
que te te estás ofendiendo a ti mismo ar
of Troy you are doing you are disgusting
de Troya estás haciendo estás dando asco
or rather apart from the fact that you are being
o sea aparte de que estás siendo
pathetic you are disgusting man you are a
patético estás dando asco tío eres un
stalker or rather directly
acosador o sea directamente